Guide to the Rice University Dean of Engineering Records, 1951-2011 UA 115
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series 7: Addenda, 1980s-2008 (Box 73)
  - Visiting Institute for Cross-Disciplinary Research Education, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Subseries: Engineering faculty
    - Aazhang, B. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Antoulas, A. (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Baraniuk, Richard (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Bedient, Phil (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Bennet, John (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Blackburn, Jim (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Bourland, Hardy (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Carroll, Michael (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Cavallaro, Joseph (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Clark, J.W. (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Esenaliev (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Felleisen, M. (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Fraser, Matt (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Goldman, Ron (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Halas, Naomi (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Hughes, Joseph (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - Johnson, Ron (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Jump, J. Robert (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Kavraki, Lydia (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Kennedy, Ken W. (Box 77, Folder 26-28)
    - Massey, Richard (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Mittleman, Dan (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Papoutsakis, E. Terry (Box 77, Folder 31)
    - Pharr, George M. (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - Ramaswamy, Bala (Box 77, Folder 33-34)
    - Rabson, Tom A. (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - Rifai, Hanadi (Box 77, Folder 36)
    - Tittle, Frank (Box 77, Folder 37)
    - Tomson, Mason B. (Box 77, Folder 38)
    - Varman, Peter (Box 77, Folder 39)
    - Ward, Herb (Box 77, Folder 40)
    - Wiesner, Mark (Box 77, Folder 41)
    - Wilson, Wm. L. Jr. (Box 77, Folder 42)
    - Young, Jim (Box 77, Folder 43)
- Series 8: Addenda, 2005-2011
  - Subject Files
    - Encyclopedia of Statistics in Quality and Reliability, 2005 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Environmental Programs at Rice, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - ES, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Environmental Programs Steering Committee (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Fabrication Facility, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Recruitment, 1990-2001 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Appointments P + T policies, 1990-2002 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Retirement, 1995-1998 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Retirement - Burrus, 2005 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Web projects, 1996-2000 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - EWEB, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Web Strategy, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Geology Geophysics Study, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - George R. Brown Hall, 1989-1992 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Graduate Research Traineeships (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Bioengineering Degree, 1989-1992 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Computational Engineering Degree, 1990-1993 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Televised Graduate Courses, 1991-1992 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Honors Co-Op Program Texas Instruments, 1985-86 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Graduate Program Ranking, 1986-1999 (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Graduate Student Recruitment, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Graduate Student Support, 1986-2000 (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Graduate Student Teaching, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Grantsmanship, 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - HiPerSoft, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Homeland Security Research, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - Houston Area Research Center, 1985-1996 (Box 78, Folder 27)
    - Kay Bailey Hutchison, 2005 (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - Hyprotech, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - Innovation, Creativity Entrepreneurship (ICE), 2002 (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - iRice, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 31)
    - Ideas from Other Universities: MIT (Box 78, Folder 32)
    - Ideas from Other Universities: MIT Web Initiative, 2001-2002 (Box 78, Folder 33)
    - Ideas from Other Universities: Stanford, 1996-1999 (Box 78, Folder 34)
    - Ideas from Other Universities: Stanford Entrepreneurship Study, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 35)
    - Ideas from Other Universities: Other universities, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 36)
    - Institute of Biosciences and Bioengineering (IBB) (2 folders), 2000-2002 (Box 78, Folder 37-38)
    - Imperial College London, 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 39)
    - Informational Technology Institute Portal Program, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 40)
    - Information Technology at Rice, 2000-2002 (Box 78, Folder 41)
    - Information Technology Initiative, 1999-2000 (Box 78, Folder 42)
    - Institute for Teaching and Learning, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 43)
    - Jude Heimel Associates, 2005-2008 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Kamen-Deka File: Segway, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Kamen-Deka File, 2001, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Koop, C. Everett, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - LACSI, 2000-2002 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Library, 1999-2001 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - LIFTE, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Lovett College, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Milby Science Institute, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Minority Recruitment, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Minority Recruitment: DGPSE-Minority Engineers, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Motorolla, 1984-1999 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Nano Bio Info, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - National Research Council, 1989-1993 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - National Science Foundation HRD 981755 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - National Science Foundation: Committee Visitors Report (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - National Science Foundation: Center for Nanotechnology, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - National University of Singapore, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - National Institute of Biomedical Imaging Bioengineering, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - NASA Specialized Center of Research Training (NSCORT) in Gravitational Biology, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - NSF Summit, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - NSF Cooperative Agreement, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - NSF Diversity Statement, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - National University of Science and Technology (NUST), 1996 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - OWLNET, 1987-1992 (Box 79, Folder 25-27)
    - OWLNET Information Systems, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - President's Council of Advisors on Science Technology, 2003-2004 (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Provost - Gene Levy, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Qualcomm, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - [Task Force] Racial Respect and Fairness, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Rice Alliance for Technology and Entrepreneurship (RATE) (5 folders), 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 3-7)
    - Rice Everywhere Network (RENE), n.d. (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Rice: The Next Century, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Rice/University of Houston joint projects, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Science Academy of South Texas, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Service Center Policy and Procedures, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Student Affairs, 2004-2005 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Student Scholars Program, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Summit of the Mind (2 folders), 1992 (Box 80, Folder 15-16)
    - Sustainable Technology, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - [Shell Center for] Sustainability (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - [Shell Center for] Sustainability: Operations and Management Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Space, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Space Utilization Study (3 folders), 1991 (Box 80, Folder 21-23)
    - Space Inventory (2 folders), 1995 (Box 80, Folder 24-25)
    - Space Inventory, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Staff Infrastructures Report, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Teaching Evaluations, 1989-99 (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Technological Relationship, 1995-1999 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Texaco, 1980-1999 (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Texas A, 1988-2004 (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Texas Center for Magnetism in Materials, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Texas Engineering Foundation, 1989-2002 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Texas Higher Education Summit, 2000-2002 (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Transformational Gifts, 1998-2000 (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Undergraduate Exit Survey, 2000-2001 (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - Undergraduate Teaching, 1988-1998 (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - University Cooperation for Atmospheric Research, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - Women in Science and Engineering, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Women's Commission, 1987-1990 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Women in Education, 1988-1994 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Wright Brothers visiting Professorship proposal, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Bioengineering Department
      - Bioengineering Degree Approval, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Bioengineering Department, 1992-2003 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Athanasiou, Kyriacos (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - Grande-Allen, Kathryn (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Hellums, David (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - McIntire, Larry (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - Mikos, Antonios (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Raphael, Robert (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - San, K.Y. (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - Shanks, Jackie (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - West, Jennifer Hill (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Computer and Information Technology Technology Institute (CITI)/Center for Research on Parallel Computation (CRPC)
      - CITI/CRPC, 1993-2000 (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - Koelbel, Charles (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Chemical Engineering (CENG)
      - CENG General Information/Correspondence, July 1994-December 1995 (Box 81, Folder 18)
      - CENG General Information, 1996-2000 (Box 81, Folder 19)
      - Armeniades, C.D. (Box 81, Folder 20)
      - Chapman, Walter (Box 81, Folder 21)
      - Appel, Matthias (Box 81, Folder 22)
      - Kobayashi, Riki (Box 81, Folder 23)
      - Miller, Clarence (Box 81, Folder 24)
      - Robert, Marc (Box 81, Folder 25)
      - San, Ka-Yin (Box 81, Folder 26)
      - Song, Kyoo (Box 81, Folder 27)
      - Wong, Michael (Box 81, Folder 28)
      - Zygourakis, K. (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Civil Engineering (CIVI)
      - Civil Engineering, 1994-1999 (Box 81, Folder 30)
      - Alvarez (Box 81, Folder 32)
      - Dakoulas, Panos (Box 81, Folder 33)
      - Durrani, Ahmad (Box 81, Folder 34)
      - Moore, Pat (Box 81, Folder 35)
      - Nagaoka, R. (Box 81, Folder 36)
      - CIVI-Ryon Fund, 1991-1992 (Box 81, Folder 37)
      - CIVI-Ryon Fund, January 1993-June 1994 (Box 81, Folder 38)
      - Terk, Michael (Box 81, Folder 39)
      - Veletsos, Anestis (Box 81, Folder 40)
    - Computational and Applied Mathematics (CAAM)
      - General Information/Correspondence, 1994-2000 (Box 81, Folder 41)
      - Applegate, David (Box 81, Folder 42)
      - Bixby, Robert E. (Box 81, Folder 43)
      - Borcea, Lydia (Box 81, Folder 44)
      - Carroll, Michael (Box 81, Folder 45)
      - Cook, William (Box 81, Folder 46)
      - Cox, Steve (Box 81, Folder 47)
      - Dennis, J.E. (Box 81, Folder 48)
      - El-Bakry, Amr (Box 81, Folder 49)
      - Embree (Box 81, Folder 50)
      - Heinkenschloss, Matthias (Box 81, Folder 51)
      - Moore, Doug (Box 81, Folder 52)
      - Moore McZeal, Cassandra (Box 81, Folder 53)
      - Scott, David (Box 81, Folder 54)
      - Sorenson, Danny (Box 81, Folder 55)
      - Symes, W.W. (Box 81, Folder 56)
      - Tapia, R.A. (Box 81, Folder 57)
      - Velazquez, Leticia (Box 81, Folder 58)
      - Villalobos, Cristina (Box 81, Folder 59)
      - Wheeler, M.E. (Box 81, Folder 60)
      - Christian, William (Box 81, Folder 61)
    - Computer Science
      - General Information/Correspondence, 1994-2003 (Box 81, Folder 62)
      - Adve, Vikram (Box 81, Folder 63)
      - Barland, Ian (Box 81, Folder 64)
      - Carle, Alan (Box 81, Folder 65)
      - Cartwright, Robert (Box 81, Folder 66)
      - Chen, Johnny (Box 81, Folder 67)
      - Clarkson, Gavin (Box 81, Folder 68)
      - Cooper, Keith (Box 81, Folder 69)
      - Cox, Alan L. (Box 81, Folder 70)
      - Druschel, Peter (Box 81, Folder 71)
    - Strategic Plan
      - Consultant - William Slebos, 2006 (Box 81, Folder 72)
      - Department Chairs/Institute Center Directors, November 11, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 73)
      - Department Chairs/Institute Center Directors, December 6, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 74)
      - Strategic Planning, November 2005 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Bioengineering, November 14, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Computer Science, November 17, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - ECE, November 18, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - CEVE, November 21, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - CAAM, November 22, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - ChBE, November 23, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Assignment from Retreat, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - MEMS, December 5, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - STAT, November 30, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - Town Hall Meeting, January 18, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Strategic Planning, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - Administrative Support, January 4-5, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - New Professors Lecture Series, 2000-2006
      - New Professors Lecture Series, 2000-01 (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - Keith Cooper, January 21, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 15)
      - Joe Warren, March 29, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - Joseph P. Hughes, September 11, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 17)
      - Walter Chapman, January 16, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 18)
      - Joseph Cavallaro, September 9, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 19)
      - Peter Druschel, February 24, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 20)
      - Michael Deem, April 2, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 21)
      - Michael Orchard, April 15, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 22)
      - Yin Zhang, February 11, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 23)
      - Devika Subramanian, March 22, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 24)
      - Pedro Alvarez, April 5, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 25)
      - Enrique Barrera, September 1, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 26)
      - Jennifer West, December 2, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 27)
      - Lydia Kavraki, February 7, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 28)
      - Andrew Meade, April 14, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 29)
      - Rudy Guerra, April 21, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 30)
      - Rebecca Richards-Kortum, August 30, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 31)
      - Sallie Keller-McNulty, January 31, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 32)
      - Boris Yakobson, March 7, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 33)
      - Matthias Heinkenschloss, March 30, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 34)
      - Edward Knightly, September 7, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 35)
    - Scholarship Information, 1993-94 (Box 82, Folder 36)
    - Rice Engineering Design Development Institute (REDDI)
      - Annual Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 82, Folder 37)
      - Council Meeting, 1984-85 (Box 82, Folder 38)
      - General Information/Correspondence, 1978-1994 (Box 82, Folder 39)
      - News Releases, 1978-1981 (Box 82, Folder 40)
      - Research Agreement/Invitation Grant Forms (Box 82, Folder 41)
      - Symposium, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 42)
      - Survey replies, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 43)
    - Rice Institute for Continuing Education in Engineering (RICEE)
      - RICEE, 1986-88 (Box 82, Folder 44)
      - RICEE, 1988-1990 (Box 82, Folder 45)
      - RICEE, 1991-1999 (Box 82, Folder 46)
      - Honors Co-Op Program, 1985-87 (Box 82, Folder 47)
      - UT/TV, 1989 (Box 82, Folder 48)
      - Commission on Colleges Co-Op Programs, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 49)
      - World Conference on Continuing Education, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 50)
      - Co-Op Programs miscellaneous publications (Box 82, Folder 51)
      - Model Agreements (Box 82, Folder 52)
      - Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 53)
      - AMCEE Association for Media Based Continuing Education for Engineers, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Annenberg/CPB Co-Op Program, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Canergie Foundation Co-Op Program (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Cornell University Co-Op Program (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - Florida Engineering Education Co-Op Program (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - IBM Co-Op Programs (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - John Hopkins Co-Op Programs (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Houston Baptist University Co-Op Programs (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - University of Houston Co-Op Program (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board (2 folders) (Box 83, Folder 10-11)
      - Tager TV Network Co-Op Network (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - SMU Co-Op Programs (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - Stanford Co-Op Programs (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - Texas Instruments Co-Op Program (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - Virginia Polytechnic Institute Co-Op Program (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - TI Co-Op Programs (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - MIT Co-Op Programs (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - NASA Co-Op Programs (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - National Technical University Co-Op Programs (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - Interact Co-Op Programs (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Media-CDs [Virtual tour of Wiess School of Natural Sciences, Dean's Presentation to Board], 2007, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Outstanding Engineering Alumni, 1998-99 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Photographs - Carroll/Conn, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Scientia, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Utility Infrastructure Report, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 26)
- Series 9: Addenda, 1990-1992
  - Energy and Environmental Systems Institute (EESI), 1990-1992 (Box 83, Folder 27)
- Series 10: Addenda, Bart Sinclair, 1983-1992
  - History of Rice Engineering Degrees (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Fax: University of Pittsburgh School of Engineering, 1998-11-06 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Graduate Survey: Engineering, Technology, and Computer Science, 1996-1997 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Rehabilitation and Additions to the Mechanical Lab and Abercrombie Buildings Rice University Programming Phase Report, 1980-01-22 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - Semiconductor Lab Renovation, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - Renovation Dyson Lab, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - Dyson Lab Renovation - Abercrombie (Shell Pilot Plant), 1983 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Chemical Engineering Renovation Phase II (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Information about Rice Graduate School for College Counsel (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Survey of Scientific and Engineering Research Facilities, 1995-11-13 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Bioengineering Grad Program (Box 84, Folder 5)